<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SAMPTA 2023</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on SAMPTA 2023</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sampta2023.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Speakers</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/speakers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/speakers/</guid><description>Plenary Speakers Our plenary speakers will include:
Soledad Villar (Johns Hopkins) Laura Balzano (University of Michigan) Samory Kpotufe (Columbia University) Mark Iwen (Michigan State University) Holger Rauhut (Aachen University) Coralia Cartis (Oxford) Rebecca Willett (University of Chicago)</description></item><item><title>Announcing SampTA 2023</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/posts/announcing-sampta-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/posts/announcing-sampta-2023/</guid><description>SampTA is back! This year&amp;rsquo;s Sampling Theory and Applications conference will be held at Yale University from July 10-14th, 2023.
Our plenary speakers will include:
Soledad Villar (Johns Hopkins) Laura Balzano (University of Michigan) Samory Kpotufe (Columbia University) Mark Iwen (Michigan State University) Holger Rauhut (Aachen University) Coralia Cartis (Oxford) Rebecca Willett (University of Chicago) Further details (including panelists, and a detailed schedule) are coming soon. We&amp;rsquo;ll keep this page updated with the latest details.</description></item><item><title>Call for Papers</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/posts/call-for-papers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/posts/call-for-papers/</guid><description>Abstract submission deadline: by the end of Friday March 10, 2023, Anywhere on Earth
Full paper submission and co-author registration deadline: Friday March 17, 2023 AoE
Supplementary materials submission deadline: Friday March 24, 2023 AoE
Author notification: Wednesday May 10, 2023 AoE
Camera-ready, poster, and video submission: Wednesday May 31, 2023 AoE
The site will start accepting submissions on: Tuesday January 10th, 2023
The 14th annual conference on Sampling Theory and Applications is an interdisciplinary forum for mathematicians, engineers, and applied scientists to share recent advances in sampling theory and discuss trends in the field and its applications.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/about/</guid><description>SampTA 2023 14th International conference on Sampling Theory and Applications SampTA (Sampling Theory and Applications) is a biennial interdisciplinary conference for mathematicians, engineers, and applied scientists. The main purpose of SampTA is to exchange recent advances in sampling theory and to explore new trends and directions in the related areas of application. The conference focuses on such fields as signal processing and image processing, coding theory, control theory, real analysis and complex analysis, harmonic analysis, and the theory of differential equations.</description></item></channel></rss>