<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SAMPTA 2023</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on SAMPTA 2023</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sampta2023.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Registration now open</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/posts/registration-now-open/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/posts/registration-now-open/</guid><description>Want to attend SampTA 2023? Excited by our wonderful slate of speakers and special sessions?
Registration is open from now until July 1st at this link. You can register either as an in-person or virtual attendee.
Registration costs $300 per person (or $150 for students). We do offer financial aid to cover both the registration fee and travel to and from New Haven; to apply, fill out this form.</description></item><item><title>Venue</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/venue/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/venue/</guid><description>SampTA&amp;rsquo;s presentations and special sessions will be in the Cohen Auditorium at the Yale School of Medicine (that&amp;rsquo;s at 230 South Frontage Road). Here&amp;rsquo;s how to find the auditorium.
There are half a dozen hotels within a five-minute walk of the auditorium, all nestled around the heart of Yale&amp;rsquo;s campus.
The Blake Hotel (2 blocks away) The New Haven Hotel (2 blocks away) The Omni New Haven (4 blocks away) The Study at Yale (5 blocks away) The Graduate (Also 5 blocks away) The Courtyard by Marriott (7 blocks away)</description></item><item><title>Financial Aid</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/aid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/aid/</guid><description>We offer the opportunity to apply for financial aid in order to support your travels or the conference registration fees. Please use this form to apply.</description></item><item><title>Speakers &amp; Sessions</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/speakers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/speakers/</guid><description>Plenary Speakers Our plenary speakers will include:
Michael Bronstein (Oxford) Gitta Kutyniok (LMU) Dan Spielman (Yale) Soledad Villar (Johns Hopkins) Samory Kpotufe (Columbia University) Mark Iwen (Michigan State University) Holger Rauhut (Aachen University) Coralia Cartis (Oxford) Rebecca Willett (University of Chicago) Special Sessions Our special sessions will bring together domain experts to present on topics including Manifold Learning from Data, Graph Signal Processing, Topological Data Analysis, and Sampling Theory for Neural Activity Data, among others.</description></item><item><title>Call for Papers</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/call-for-papers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/call-for-papers/</guid><description>⭐ Submissions are live at our Open Review page ⭐
Full paper submission and co-author registration deadline: April 01, 2023 AoE (Note: previously, there were separate deadlines for the abstract and paper submission. These are now combined, and the deadline has been extended. You needn&amp;rsquo;t submit anything before April 1st.)
Author notification: Wednesday May 10, 2023 AoE
Camera-ready, poster, and video submission: Wednesday May 31, 2023 AoE
The site will start accepting submissions on: Friday January 9th, 2023</description></item><item><title>Announcing SampTA 2023</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/posts/announcing-sampta-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/posts/announcing-sampta-2023/</guid><description>SampTA is back! This year&amp;rsquo;s Sampling Theory and Applications conference will be held at Yale University from July 10-14th, 2023.
We have a Call for Papers on sampling theory, signal and image processing, and data analysis. Papers accepted by SampTA will be published in a special issue of Sampling Theory, Signal Processing, and Data Analysis.
Our Plenary Speakers will include Coralia Cartis, Rebecca Willett, and Mark Iwen, among many others. See our full list here.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://sampta2023.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sampta2023.github.io/about/</guid><description>SampTA 2023 14th International conference on Sampling Theory and Applications This year&amp;rsquo;s Sampling Theory and Applications conference will be held at Yale University from July 10-14th, 2023.
We have a Call for Papers on sampling theory, signal and image processing, and data analysis. Papers accepted by SampTA will be published in a special issue of Sampling Theory, Signal Processing, and Data Analysis.
Our Plenary Speakers will include Coralia Cartis, Rebecca Willett, and Mark Iwen, among many others.</description></item></channel></rss>